Preliminary Guide to the Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) records, 1867-2006 MS2195
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Court cases, 1867 - 1989; 1949-1989; Series 5
  - Supremt Ct. no. 79-1588 Amicus brief of Kentucky in support of appellants, 1980 May 29; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Supreme Ct. no 80-975 Federal respondents in opposition, 1980; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Sure Tan Inc vs. Chicago Leather Workers Union, etc., undated; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Sure-Tan Inc vs. National Labor Relations Board, 1984 June 25; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Sure-Tan Inc vs. National Labor Relations Board, 1984 June 25; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Sure-Tan Inc vs. National Labor Relations Board, 1984 June 25; Series 5 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Sure Tan Inc vs. NLPR: memo, 1984 October 4; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Tacynec vs. City of Philadelphia, 1982 September 2; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Takahashi vs. Fish and game commission, 1948 June 7; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Tameny vs. Atlantic richfield co., 1980 June 2; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Taylor vs. Brighton corp., 1980 February 14; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Taylor vs. Taylor, 1963 May 28; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Testimony, 1981-1983; Series 5 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Texas highway comm'n suit, undated; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Texas dept. of community affairs vs. Burdine, 1981 March 4; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Texas state AFL-CIO vs. Kennedy, 1964 March 18; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Texas vs. Sifuentes, 1987 July 23; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Thomas vs. Review board of the Indiana employment security division, 1981 April 6; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Thomas vs. Rohner-Gehrig and co., 1984 March 14; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Transcontinental and western air vs. Civil Aeronautics Board, 1949 April 18; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Treat vs. White, 1901 April 29; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Unexcelled chem corp vs. United States, 1953 March 9; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - United auto workers vs. Brock, 1986 June 25; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - United States vs. Aguilar, Clark, etc., 1989 March 30; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - United States vs. American telephone and telegraph co., 1977 October 20; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - United States vs. Brignoni-Fonce, 1975 June 30; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - United States vs. Clark, et. al, 1982 January 12; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - United States vs. Cortez, 1981 January 21; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - United States vs. Dawlett, 1986 April 2; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - United States vs. Dean, 1984 March 5; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - United States vs. Del Socorro Pardo DeAguilar, 1985 January; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - United States vs. Dos Santos, 1989 July 6; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - United States vs. Eilberg, 1980 June 25; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - United States vs. Fedorenko, 1978 July 25; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - United States vs. Feola, 1975 March 19; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - United States vs. Hooker chemical, 1984 November 15; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - United States vs. Igbatayo, 1985; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 39)
  - United States vs. Kagama, 1886 May 10; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - United States vs. Larionoff, 1977 June 13; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - United States vs. Lee, 1982 February 23; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - United States vs. Los Angeles, complaint for violation of voting rights act, 1985 November 26; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - United States vs. Los Angeles, memo in support of motion to dismiss, 1986 May 5; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - United States vs. Los Angeles, motion to dismiss, 1986 March 24; Series 5 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - United States vs. Mendoza-Lopez, 1986 October; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - United States vs. Merkt, 1986 July 17; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - United States vs. Ortiz, 1975 June 30; Series 5 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - United States vs. Petrella, 1983 May 11; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - United States vs. Prince line, ltd., 1951 May 16; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - United States vs. Qaisi, 1985 December 19; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - United States vs. Reserve mining co., 1972 June 15; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - United States vs. Robinson, 1973 March 23; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - United States vs. Shaughnessy, 1957 March 25; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - United States vs. State examiners of electricians, 1985 June 25; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - United States vs. Stevart, 1931 March 2; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - United States vs. Stone and downer co., 1927 May 16; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - United States vs. Students chal. reg. agcy. pro., 1973 June 18; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - United States vs. Texas, 1971 December 6; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - United States vs. 86.9 cases, 1971 November 19; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - United States ex rel. Jolly vs. Reimer, 1935 May 21; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - United States ex rel. Knauff vs. Shaughnessy, 1950 January 16; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - United States ex rel. Leibovitz vs. IRS and INS (1/2), 1987; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 40)
  - United States ex rel. Leibovitz vs. IRS and INS (2/2), 1987; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  - United States ex rel. Leslie vs. Potomac electric power co., 1953 September 17; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - United States ex rel. Rizzo vs. Curnan, 1925 November 20; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - United States postal service vs. Brennan, 1978 June 7; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - University of California vs. Heckler, 1985 April 2; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - University of Texas vs. Comenisch, 1981; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Valley forge christian college vs. Americans united for separation of church and state inc., 1982 January 12; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Variamparambil vs. INS, 1987 October 15; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Vazquez vs. IN employment sec. div., 1985 December 30; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Velasquez vs. Sec of HHS, 1984 February 14; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Vespremi vs. Giles, 1980 April 9; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Viccaro vs. Andressen, 1964; Series 5 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Vigile vs. Sava, 1982 March 5; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Villegas vs. Snake River Farmers, 1986 May 19; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Villegas vs. Snake River Farmers Assn, 1986; Series 5 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Virginia agricultural growers asso vs. US dept of labor, 1985 March 13; Series 5 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Vogel vs. American society of appraisers, 1984 September 20; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Wall vs. INS, 1984 January 3; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Wallace vs. Jaffree, 1985 June 4; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Wang vs. INS, 1979 August 10; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Warth vs. Seldin, 1975 June 25; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Water transport association vs. Interstate commerce commission, 1987 June 5; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Watt vs. Alaska, 1981 April 21; Series 5 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Wells vs. Alropa corporation, 1936 March 9; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Wickes vs. Olympic airways, 1984 October 3; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Wilderness society vs. Griles, 1987 July 14; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Willacoohee vs. Baldrige, 1983 January 31; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Williams vs. Lee optical co., 1955 March 28; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Williams vs. Rhodes, 1968 October 15; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Williams vs. Virginia state board of elections, 1968 July 16; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Wisconsin vs. Yoder, et. al, 1972 May 15; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Witco chemical co. vs. United States, 1984 August 23; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Woolford reality co. vs. Rose, 1932 May 16; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Wright vs. United States, 1938 January 17; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Yolano-Donnelly vs. Pierce correspondence and research, undated; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Yolano-Donnelly vs. Pierce defendant's motion, 1986 August 20; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Yolano-Donnelly vs. Pierce defendant's reply, 1986 September 15; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Yolano-Donnelly vs. Pierce memo, 1986 August; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Yolano-Donnelly vs. Pierce memo of points and authorities, 1986 July 15; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Yolano-Donnelly vs. Pierce plaintiff's reply, 1986 September 8; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Young vs. Klutznick, 1980 September 25; Series 5 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Zurmati vs. McMahon, 1986 April 23; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Audio Visual records, 1996-1997; Series 6
  Arranged in episode order.
  This series contains video of the television show BorderLine.
  - BorderLine, 1996-1997; Series 6 (Box 142)
    General
    episodes: #1,3-7,9-11, 13-16, 19-21, 23-25, 27, 29-30, 33-34, 37, 41-43, 45, 47-51
  - BorderLine, 1996-1997; Series 6 (Box 143)
    Episodes #2, 8, 12, 17-18, 26, 28, 31-32, 35, 38-39, 44, 46
- Press and publicity, 1973-1996; Series 7
  This series contains press releases and newspaper and journal articles. These articles and press releases are about and produced by FAIR. These records date from 1973-1996.
  - Amnesty Articles, 1988; Series 7 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Amnesty Articles, 1988; Series 7 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Border Disputes, 1989; Series 7 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Bureau of census position on HR. 2661, 1989 September 7; Series 7 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Census lawsuit: press releases, undated; Series 7 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Census suit press, 1980; Series 7 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Census press release, 1989; Series 7 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Cleveland Plain Dealer, 1982; Series 7 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1987; Series 7 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Clippings: census and illegal aliens (1/2), 1989; Series 7 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Clippings: census and illegal aliens (2/2), 1989; Series 7 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Clippings: immigration bill, 1982; Series 7 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Coalition for Constitutional Reapportionment press releases, undated; Series 7 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Consular Affairs Press Clips, 1990 May-June; Series 7 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Dead clips, 1987; Series 7 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Ebony Magazine, 1979; Series 7 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Employer sanctions, 1987-1990; Series 7 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Equilibrium, 1973; Series 7 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Evans-Novak column, 1983; Series 7 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - FAIR clippings, 1980-1981; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - FAIR clippings, 1981-1984; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - FAIR clippings, 1982-1983; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - FAIR clippings, 1983-1984; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - FAIR clippings, 1984; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - FAIR clippings, 1984-1987; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - FAIR clippings, 1987; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - FAIR clippings, 1987-1988; Series 7 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - FAIR clippings, 1990 July-August; Series 7 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - FAIR clippings, 1990 September-December; Series 7 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - FAIR clippings, 1991 January-June; Series 7 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - FAIR clippings, 1991 July-October; Series 7 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - FAIR clippings, 1991 October-December; Series 7 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - FAIR clippings, 1992 January-March; Series 7 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - FAIR in the news, 1986; Series 7 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - FAIR in the news, 1986 June 30 - 1986 December 31; Series 7 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - FAIR in the news, 1986 June 30 - 1986 December 31; Series 7 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - FAIR in the news, 1986-1987; Series 7 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - FAIR in the news, 1986-1987; Series 7 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - FAIR in the news, 1986-1987; Series 7 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - FAIR in the news, 1986-1987; Series 7 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - FAIR in the news, 1987-1988; Series 7 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - FAIR in the news, 1987-1988; Series 7 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - FAIR in the news, 1987 October; Series 7 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - FAIR in the news, 1987 December; Series 7 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - FAIR in the news, 1988 January; Series 7 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - FAIR in the news, 1988 July 1 - December 1; Series 7 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - FAIR media files, 1986; Series 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - FAIR vs. Klutznick media (1/3), undated; Series 7 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - FAIR vs. Klutznick media (2/3), undated; Series 7 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - FAIR vs. Klutznick media (3/3), undated; Series 7 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Fresno Bee, undated; Series 7 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Fundraising articles, 1987; Series 7 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Grand Rapids Press, 1979; Series 7 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Immigration Articles, 1990 August; Series 7 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Immigration press clippings (1/3), 1991; Series 7 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Immigration press clippings (2/3), 1991; Series 7 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Immigration press clippings (3/3), 1991; Series 7 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - INS news conference, 1987 March 16; Series 7 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - INS press conference, 1987 April 30; Series 7 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - INS press conference, 1986 November 25; Series 7 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - INS press conference, 1987 July 20; Series 7 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - INS press conference, 1988 January 13; Series 7 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Law review articles on deportation procedures, 1983-1988; Series 7 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - List of shows and interviews, 1984-1989; Series 7 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - MacNeil-Lehrer news hour, 1987 November 23; Series 7 (Box 144, Folder 21)
  - Miami Herald, 1980-1982; Series 7 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - News advisory and releases, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - News clippings, 1983 November; Series 7 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - News clippings (1/2), 1990 June-August; Series 7 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - News clippings (2/2), 1990 June-August; Series 7 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Opponents rhetoric, 1977-1986; Series 7 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Press conference, 1987 July 20; Series 7 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Press conference, Houston TX, 1990 June 4; Series 7 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Press conference on labor market impact on immigration., 1982 December 7; Series 7 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Press extras, 1988-1989; Series 7 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Press release, 1982 March 17; Series 7 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, 1980-1989; Series 7 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, 1985; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Press releases, 1985-1986; Series 7 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Press releases, 1987; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, 1989; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, 1990; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Press releases, 1991; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Press releases, 1992; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Press releases, 1994; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, 1993; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, 1995; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Press releases, 1996; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Press releases, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Press releases, undated; Series 7 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Press releases: received, 1987-1988; Series 7 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Press releases: sent, 1987-1989; Series 7 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Trade clips, 1987; Series 7 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of appearance on 'The Today Show', 1987 September 16; Series 7 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - White house press release, 1986 November 6; Series 7 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - WTVS special advisory board, 1988; Series 7 (Box 144, Folder 25)
- Subject files, 1974-2006; Series 8
  This series contains subject files maintained by FAIR to assist with operations and research. These materials date from 1977-2006 and cover many topics related to immigration issues.
  Organized into 12 subseries: People [1998 accretion], People [2007 accretion], States and cities [1998 accretion], States [2007 accretion], Federal departments and offices, General subject files, Immigration and Naturalization Service, Organizations, Countries, Fair publications, Publications, and Center for Immigration Studies.
  - People [1998 accretion], 1977-1992; Series 8 subseries 1
    This subseries contains subject files gathered to research specific individuals and their work related to issues of immigration. These files date from 1977-1992. In addition, subseries 4 contains subject files for individuals. The records in subseries 4 were donated separately from this subseries and have not been merged. Both subseries should be searched to ensure throughness.
    - Abbot, Charles, 1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Abram, Elliot, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Abdnor, James S. (R-SD), 1984-1985; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Adams, Brock (D-WA), 1988-1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Alexander, Bill (D-AR), 1983-1984, 1986, 1988-1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Allen, Andrew, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Allen, George (R-VA), 1991-1992; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Anderegg, Phillip, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Anderson, Glenn M. (D-CA), 1983-1984, 1986, 1989, 1991-1992; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Anderson, John, 1979-1980; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Andrews, Mark (R-ND), 1983; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Annunzio, Frank (D-IL), 1983-1986, 1988, 1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Anthony, Beryl F., Jr. (D-AR), 1988; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Atiyeh, Victor, 1981; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Atkins, Chester G. (D-MA), 1988-1989, 1992; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Au Coin, Les (D-OR), 1983-1986, 1988-1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Ault, Bromwell, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Baker, Howard H., Jr. (TN), 1979-1983; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Barnard, Doug (D-GA), 1984-1985.1988-1989.1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Beaver, Brad, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Bennett, Charles E. (D-FL), 1983-1986, 1988-1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Berckmueller, David, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Boner, William (D-TN), 1981, 1983-1984; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Boogher, John, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Boohaker, Joseph, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Boyle, J. Bayard, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Broomfield, William (R-MI), 1983, 1988-1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Brown, Jean, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Brown, Jerry, 1979; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Browne, Margaret, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Bruce, Terry (D-IL), 1988-1989, 1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Bruckner, H.A., undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Bruen, Alex, 1982-1983; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Buckley, William F., 1980; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Burbank, Nelson, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Burdick, Quentin N. (D-ND), 1981-1983, 1987-1989, 1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Bush, George, 1979-1980; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Bustamente, Albert (D-TX), 1985-1986, 1988-1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Byron, Beverly (D-ND), 1983-1984, 1988; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Campbell, Tom (R-CA), 1989-1990, 1992; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Capraro, Franz, 1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Carlson, Delmar, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Carper, Thomas (D-DE), 1983-1984, 1988-1989, 1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Cartwright, Clarke, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Casillas, Richard, 1981-1982; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Castillo, Leonel, 1977-1980; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Chandler, Rod (R-MA), 1983-1986, 1988-1989, 1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Chase, Edward M., undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Chip, Bill, 1980-1981; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Clark, Dick, 1979; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Clements,Bill (TX), 1982; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Coleman, E. Thomas (R-MO), 1984-1986, 1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Collard, William Edwin, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Colter, Tim, 1987; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Connally, John, 1979; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Cook, Joe, 1979; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Cott, Peter, 1979; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Coughlin, Lawrence (R-PA), 1983-1984, 1989-1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Cowan, James, 1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Crain, Rance, 1981; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Cranston, Alan (D-CA), 1977, 1981-1992; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Cronkite, Walter, 1980; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Crosland, David, 1980; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Crossman, Rober, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Crystal, Margaret, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Curtis, Gregory, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Dannemeyer, William (R-CA), 1983-1984, 1986, 1988-1989, 1992; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Danilov, Dan P., undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Davidson, James, 1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Davis, Gregory, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Davis, Robert (R-MI), 1982-1986, 1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Denton, Jeremiah (AL), 1984-1985; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Deutschbein, Mary, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Dickinson, William (R-AL), 1984, 1989, 1991-1992; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Dietrich, Janet, 1981; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Dillingham, Marian, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Dixon, Alan J. (D-IL), 1982-1983, 1986, 1987, 1989-1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Donnelly, Brian (D-MA), 1983-1984, 1987-1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Dornan, Robert (R-CA), 1986, 1988-1992; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Douglas, Eugene, 1982; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Downey, Thomas (D-NY), 1983-1984, 1991; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Downs Carpet Co. Inc, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - Dubs, Emil E., 1988; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Dudley, Craig, 1989; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 23)
    - Dudley, Tilford, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 24)
    - Dunn, Clay, undated; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 148, Folder 25)
    - Dwyer, Bernard (D-NJ), 1984, 1992; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Dymally, Mervyn (D-CA), 1983-1984, 1980-1988; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Eagleton, Thomas F. (MO), 1984-1985; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Early, Joseph (D-MA), 1984, 1989, 1991-1992; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - East, John P. (NC), 1984-1985; Series 8 subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 25)